loyaltyplus.aero 2015-04-11

# Privacy Policy » Loyalty Plus

### Privacy Policy of LoyaltyPlus

**To Our Clients:**

Our clients’ privacy is important to us, and maintaining our clients’ trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect our clients’ right to keep their data and personal information confidential and understand their desire to avoid unwanted solicitations.

All data privacy is addressed though customer contractual agreements. We only collect information about our clients when that information is provided by our clients or is obtained by us with their authorization.

In accordance with the contractual agreements with our clients, we do not disclose business or personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone.

**Confidentiality and Security of Non-public Personal Information**

We restrict access to non-public business and personal information about our clients to employees of our firm.  Our employees’ right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our firm, our Confidentiality and Non-Disclosure Agreements and applicable law. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable client contracts, laws and regulations to guard our clients’ business and personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or premature destruction.

We value the business and trust relationship with our clients and are committed to protecting their data privacy.

**LoyaltyPlus Accolades (Pty) Ltd**

This website uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you are giving consent to cookies being used. More information. ×
